

Md Ashaduzzaman

Date of birth: 25/12/1990 **Nationality:** Bangladeshi

Gender: Male

CONTACT

- Khondokar Para,5840 Sherpur, Bangladesh(Home)
- mukul.ashad@gmail.com
- (+880) 01724639919
- https://github.com/ mukul531410
- f https://www.facebook.com/ mukul.ashad
- https://twitter.com/ mukul531410
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ashaduzzaman-6b646b21/
- S ashad.epl (Skype)



ABOUT ME

Passionate WordPress Developer with 7+ years of working experience. I'm an expert in the front-end and WordPress back-end. I can build custom themes from the sketch, develop WordPress theme, customize any WordPress themes or plugin, optimization websites, bug fixing. My core competency lies in clean, semantic, and SEO friendly coding with 100% W3C validation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/09/2021 - CURRENT New York, United States

WordPress Developer Level III Kings Crest Global

- Designing and implementing new features and functionality
- Establishing and guiding the website's architecture
- Ensuring high-performance and availability, and managing all technical aspects of the CMS
- Helping formulate an effective, responsive design and turning it into a working theme and plugin.

01/04/2017 - 31/08/2021 Benowa, Australia

WordPress Developer NETMOW

- Develop WordPress website from scratch
- Customize WordPress theme
- Develop WordPress Plugin from scratch
- Update, Modify, Add new features existing project
- Fixing issues and improvement performance

01/01/2016 - 31/03/2017 Dhaka, Bangladesh

Web developers Mediusware

- Develop WordPress website from scratch
- Customize WordPress theme
- Develop WordPress Plugin from scratch
- Update, Modify, Add new features existing project
- Fixing issues and improvement performance

01/08/2014 - 19/12/2014 Dhaka, Bangladesh

Junior Web Developer Instalogic BD

- PSD to HTML
- HTML to WordPress theme development
- Cross-browser compatibility issue
- Fix issue
- Maintain existing projects

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Bengali

Other language(s):

English

Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	Writing
B2	B2	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/07/2009 - 06/07/2013 Dhaka, Bangladesh

Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering Dhaka International University

Website https://diu.ac/

01/06/2005 - 01/09/2009 Bogura, Bangladesh

Diploma in Computer Engineering Institute of Information Technology Bogura
Website https://www.iitb.edu.bd/

01/01/2003 – 31/03/2005 Sherpur, Bangladesh

Secondary School Certificate Sherpur Gov. Model D.J High School

DIGITAL SKILLS

WordPress | Woocommerce | Experience with PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript | Web development languages: PHP, HTML5, CSS | Version Control System (Git) | WordPress Plugin Development | Elementor Page Builder | Visual Composer | Visual Studio - Visual basic | WEB DESIGN: HTML, SCSS, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, BOOTSTRAP, MATERIAL UI | Advanced Custom Fields | Bug tracking Systems: Jira